globalgascard.com 2012-10-04

# Global Gas Card

                                        Global Gas Card
                                                 Privacy Policy
INFORMATION COLLECTION
Global Gas Card, LLC (referred to herein as “Global Gas Card”, “our”, “us” or “we”) is the sole owner of
the information collected on our websites and on the replicated Global Gas Card websites that we provide
for use by independent contractor Distributors (hereafter the “websites”). We collect information from
Independent Distributors (“Distributors”), customers and visitors to the websites at different points on the
websites.
Personally Identifiable Information
Through your use of or visits to our websites, you may be required or requested to provide personally
identifiable information to us. Personally identifiable information is any piece of information which can
potentially be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person including names, addresses,
email addresses, telephone numbers, social security and tax identification numbers, and credit card
information.
Distributor and Customer Registration
In order to become a Distributor, an applicant must provide biographical and contact information (such as
name, mailing address, telephone numbers, and email address) to us. We also require an applicant’s
Social Security Number or Federal Tax ID Number so that we may prepare and file necessary non-
employee compensation forms for the IRS. Certain customers may be required to register in order to
purchase products directly from us (“Registered Customers”). Registered Customers will be required to
provide contact information (such as name, mailing address, telephone number(s), and email address)
and payment information (such as credit card or checking account information). We use this information
to maintain contact with Distributors and Registered Customers, and to process Distributor and
Registered Customer orders.
Downline Genealogy Reports
As a network marketing company, Global Gas Card provides certain information to Distributors regarding
the other Distributors and Registered Customers enrolled in a Distributor’s downline marketing
organization. If you enroll as a Distributor or Registered Customer with Global Gas Card, your name,
address, email address, and telephone number will be provided to your enroller. No other personally
identifiable information will be shared with other Distributors. Such information is made available to
Global Gas Card Distributors subject to a confidentiality and non-disclosure covenant in the agreement
that each Distributor enters into with Global Gas Card.
Product or Service Purchases
When a customer, Registered Customer, or Distributor purchases products or services from us through
any of our websites, the purchaser must provide us with mailing and contact information as well as
payment information. This information is used for billing and payment purposes and to fill orders.
INFORMATION USE
Personally Identifiable Information
Personally identifiable information that is collected from customers, Distributors and Registered
Customers through Distributor and Customer Registration, Product or Services Purchases and/or Surveys
is used as described above. Global Gas Card DOES NOT share personally identifiable information
except as may be necessary to process and fill an order. Global Gas Card may share aggregated
information from time to time with its partners, vendors or other third parties. When such aggregate
information is shared by Global Gas Card, no personally identifiable information is shared.
Profile Information
Global Gas Card stores information that it collects through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties
to create a profile of visitors to our websites (“users”), including customers, Registered Customers, and
Distributors. A profile is stored information that Global Gas Card keeps on individual users that details
their viewing preferences. Profile information is tied to the user’s personally identifiable information to

                                        Global Gas Card
provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. Global Gas Card does not share profile
information with other third parties.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a
cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on the websites. Global Gas
Card uses both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close
the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s
hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet
browser help file directions.
By setting a cookie on a user’s computer, users do not have to log in a password more than once,
thereby saving time while at the websites. If a user rejects the cookie, the user will still be able to use the
site. The only drawback to this is that the user may need to enter his or her password every time he or
she accesses the site.
Log Files
Like most standard website servers Global Gas Card’s websites use log files. This includes internet
protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type,
date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the
aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not
linked to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to
enable our web-based service. We use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.
Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)
Global Gas Card employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that
help Global Gas Card to better manage content on the websites by informing it what content is effective.
Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the
online movements of users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the
page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are tied to
users’ personally identifiable information. Clear gifs are not tied to users’ personally identifiable
information.
In addition, Global Gas Card uses clear gifs in its HTML-based emails to let it know which emails have
been opened by the recipients. This allows Global Gas Card to gauge the effectiveness of certain
communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.
COMMUNICATIONS FROM US
Special Offers and Updates
Global Gas Card sends all new Distributors and Registered Customers a welcoming email to verify
password, username, and acceptance of the Distributor Agreement or Customer Agreement. All
Distributors and Registered Customers will occasionally receive information on products, services, special
deals, and a newsletter. Customers who have not registered with Global Gas Card and who grant
permission will also receive occasional information on products, services, special deals, and the like.
Service Announcements
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our
service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send Distributors and/or customers an email.
Generally, Distributors may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their
account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.
Distributor and Customer Service
Global Gas Card communicates with Distributors and Registered Customers via email, regular mail and
telephone on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their
Global Gas Card business. Global Gas Card communicates with other customers with respect to

                                        Global Gas Card
products or services purchased by such customers from Global Gas Card. Such communications may be
by email, regular mail or telephone.
SHARING
Legal Disclaimer
Though Global Gas Card makes every effort to preserve user privacy, Global Gas Card may need to
disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action
is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on Global
Gas Card.
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
Global Gas Card shares aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is
not linked to any personally identifiable information.
These are the instances in which we will share users’ personal information:
Global Gas Card DOES NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information about users with any Third
Parties.
Third Party Fulfillment
Global Gas Card uses an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing
company to bill Distributors for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use
personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Service Providers
Global Gas Card partners with other third parties to provide specific services. When necessary to provide
services or products to Distributors, Registered Customers, and other customers, we share names and/or
other contact information with service providers and vendors. Such third parties are not allowed to use
personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Business Transitions
In the event Global Gas Card goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by
another company, or selling a portion of its assets, the personal information of Distributors and customers
will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. If as a result of the business transition, a
Distributor’s or customer’s personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that
stated at the time of collection, the Distributor or customer will be given choice consistent with our
notification of changes section.
Choice
Users are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so
users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require
an outside party.
Links
Global Gas Card’s websites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Global Gas Card is not
responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage users to be aware when they
leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally
identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Global Gas Card
websites.
Security
Global Gas Card takes every precaution to protect all users’ information. When users submit sensitive
information via Global Gas Card’s websites, their information is protected both online and off-line.
When the Distributor Application, Customer Registration, and/or online order forms ask users to enter
sensitive information (such as Bank Account number and/or social security number), that information is
encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure

                                        Global Gas Card
page, such as the Distributor Application and Agreement and online order forms, the lock icon on the
bottom of web browsers such as Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as
opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’.
While Global Gas Card uses SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, the Company also
does everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All user information, not just the
sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in Global Gas Card’s offices. Only employees who
need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information.
ALL employees are kept up-to-date on Company security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that
store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment.
MISCELLANEOUS
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Global Gas Card reserves the right to amend or change this Privacy Policy at any time at its sole
discretion. It is your responsibility to periodically access this Privacy Policy by clicking on the Privacy
Policy link at our home page. When material changes or amendments are made to the Privacy Policy, we
will announce the same at our home page for a period of 10 days following implementation of the
amended Privacy Policy.
Making Changes to Your Personally Identifiable Information
Distributors and Registered Customers may update your personal information as necessary by editing it
in their back office.
Protecting Children
Global Gas Card is committed to the safety of our children. Persons under the age of 18 may not enroll
as Global Gas Card Distributors or register as customers. Children under the age of 13 may not
purchase products through any of our websites. We do not knowingly collect any personal information
from such children at this site or any of its other sites.
Effective Date
The effective date of this Privacy Policy is March 3, 2011.
